inserbia.info 2013-12-08

# Privacy Policy – InSerbia News

This document sets out the privacy policy of InSerbia network of websites (“InSerbia”) and explains how we collect and use your data. Your privacy is important to us.

#### What information do we collect about you?

We collect information from you when you register on InSerbia, when you fill in forms on our website, and when you use the site. This includes (but not limited to):

##### Your profile:

Your User Name / Nickname will be publicised on the InSerbia websites and this will be the identity by which you are known on the website. Visitors to InSerbia will be able to see limited information about you. Always think carefully about the information which you disclose on your profile. As stated in our terms of use it is your responsibility to decide what information you wish to make available to other Internet users.

##### Your email address:

We may use your email address for contacting you. Other members / visitors of InSerbia websites will also use this e-mail address as a way of contacting you.

##### Your password:

We will encrypt your password in our database. We strongly encourage you to choose a secure password that isn’t easily guessable. You should never reveal your InSerbia password to anyone. If you think your password might be compromised please change it immediately via the ‘Your account’ page.

##### Your photos:

If you choose to add a picture, this will be displayed to everyone. Don’t post images that you are not willing to be shown to everyone.

##### Your customer service history:

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

#### How will we use this information?

We may use your information when developing improvements to the site. Personally identifiable information may be used for troubleshooting any issues you might have.

#### Sharing your information with other third parties

We may in some cases use third parties to assist us in operating the site and to conduct some processing of your information on our behalf but this is always subject to strict contractual control. These third parties may be located outside the EU & US. We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are legally obliged to do so by a statutory authority with the appropriate jurisdiction, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use; or to protect the rights, property or safety of InSerbia owners, our customers, our website visitors, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection.

#### Destroying your account

Please contact us for this matter.

#### Send to friend

If you use the ‘Send to friend’ feature to tell someone about something you saw on InSerbia website, we will send an email message to the address you give us. We won’t share this email address with anyone else. By choosing to use the ‘Send to friend’ feature you are confirming that your friend is happy to receive the email. You must not use our ‘Send to friend’ feature to send spam.

#### Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users browsing patterns, and does not identify any individual info.

Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us: to estimate our audience size and usage pattern; to store information about your preferences for the site, and so allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests. This includes remembering your login details, and your preferences for displaying your ‘Edit profile’ page (if there is one); to speed up your searches; to recognize you when you return to our site.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

#### Data security

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will take all reasonable measures to ensure the security of your data, including using a third party to audit our security measures, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

#### Contact Us

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy, the way in which we use information we hold about you, if you would like to obtain a copy of the personal data we hold on you, or if you wish to make a complaint or comment: complaint@inserbia.info

#### Changes to this policy

We are constantly looking for new ways to improve this website. We may amend this privacy policy from time to time. All such changes will take effect once they have been posted on the site and you will be deemed to have accepted any such changes by your use of the site from time to time.
